//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"Which player has scored the most goals in the premier league history?",
        answer: "Alan Shearer",
        options:[
            "Wayne Rooney",
            "Micheal Owen",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Alan Shearer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Which team had won the most number of titles in the premier league?",
        answer: "Manchester United",
        options:[
            "Manchester United",
            "Chelsea Football club",
            "Arsenal",
            "Manchester City"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Which club has gone the longest without winning a game at the start of the premier league?",
        answer: "Sheffield United",
        options:[
            "NewCastle united",
            "Queens park Rangers F.C.",
            "Sheffield United",
            "Derby County"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"What is the Highest Attendance in a premier league match?",
        answer: "83,222",
        options:[
            "83,222",
            "95,023",
            "91,200",
            "75,554"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which team won the first ever premier League?",
        answer: "Manchester United",
        options:[
            "Arsenal",
            "Aston Villa",
            "Manchester United",
            "Liverpool"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Which is the Highest scoring game in the premier league along with scores?",
        answer: "Portsmouth vs Reading(7-4)",
        options:[
            "Portsmouth vs Reading(7-4)",
            "Manchester United vs Arsenal(8-2)",
            "Arsenal vs NewCastle United(7-3)",
            "Norwich City vs Southampton(4-5)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Which player has the most assist in premier league?",
        answer: "Ryan Giggs",
        options:[
            "David Silva",
            "James Milner",
            "Cesc Fabregas",
            "Ryan Giggs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Which player has scored the first ever premier League goal?",
        answer: "Briane Deane",
        options:[
            "Ian Wright",
            "Teddy Sheringham",
            "Briane Deane",
            "Andrew Cole"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"Which premier league manager has the most number of trophies?",
        answer: "Sir Alex Ferguson",
        options:[
            "Pep Guardiola",
            "Arsene Wenger",
            "Sir Alex Ferguson",
            "Sam Allardyce"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Which goalkeeper has the most number of clean sheets in premier league History?",
        answer: "Nigel Martyn",
        options:[
            "Nigel Martyn",
            "David Seaman",
            "Ederson",
            "Petr Cech"
        ]
    },
];